<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting started on Project Dovetail™ - Docs and Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting started on Project Dovetail™ - Docs and Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickstart</title>
      <link>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>We think it is awesome that you want to get started with Project Flogo! To get started you don&amp;rsquo;t even need to install anything other than Docker!
  Timers are great to schedule stuff, and a great way to learn new technology! Use this lab to get familiar with some of the concepts of Flogo!      Hello World! This lab will walk you through building your first API with Project Flogo     After you&amp;rsquo;re done with these samples, why not check out the other labs we have for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo Web UI</title>
      <link>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/getting-started-webui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/getting-started-webui/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started For an overview of how to get started, check out the Quickstart guide
Installing the Project Flogo Web UI Installing the Project Flogo Web UI is quite simple and requires nothing more than Docker pre-installed on your machine to fetch the Docker image.
Fetching and starting the Web UI To get started with the latest version of the Flogo Web UI paste this command in a terminal window:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo CLI</title>
      <link>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/getting-started-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dovetail.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/getting-started/getting-started-cli/</guid>
      <description>Before you get started Before you can get started with the cli tools you need to make sure you the Go programming language installed.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to set your GOPATH variable and make sure that $GOPATH/bin is part of your path. (see here or here for more details)
 Also make sure that you have installed dep dependency management tool.
Installing the cli tools Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve installed the Go programming language and dep there are a few commands you can run to install the cli and make developing with the cli tools even easier</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>