<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Labs on Project Dovetail™ - Docs and Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Labs on Project Dovetail™ - Docs and Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/artifacts/composer-project-template/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/artifacts/composer-project-template/readme/</guid>
      <description>This is a template project for Project Dovetail™ asset modeling, it contains the required resource definitions in the system namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/corda_network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/corda_network/</guid>
      <description>Test IOU Smart Contract in R3 Cora Network We will use Corda Demo Bench, install it if you don&amp;rsquo;t have it installed already.
1. Start up Corda Demo Bench  Click on &amp;ldquo;+Add CorDapp&amp;rdquo; button then browse to corda directory, select a jar to add(you can only add one jar at a time). Repeat, until all jars are added. You can replace kotlin-IOU-1.0.0.jar with your own. Start up 3 nodes: Notary, charlie, alice, and bob Make sure they are all running before continuing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/fabric_network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/fabric_network/</guid>
      <description>Test IOU chaincode in Hyperledger Fabric Network We need four docker images in order for &amp;ldquo;dev mode&amp;rdquo; to run against the supplied docker compose script. If you installed the fabric-samples repo clone and followed the instructions to download-platform-specific-binaries, then you should have the necessary Docker images installed locally.
1. open a terminal, and execute following command to start up the network  docker-compose -f docker-compose-simple.yaml up
 open a terminal window, run docker ps, make sure container cli, chaincode, peer, orderer and couchdb are running</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Simple IOU Smart Contract Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/iou-smart-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/dovetail/labs/iou-smart-app/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will walk you through the steps to model, implement and test smart contracts on distributed ledger technology platform of your choice. The example is a simple &amp;ldquo;I owe you&amp;rdquo; use case, the issuer of an IOU is obligated to pay the owner of the IOU amount issued, the ownership of the IOU can be transferred by current owner, and all transactions will be recorded on the ledger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>